imediabiz.com 2010-06-14

# Hosting Australia - Cheap Web Hosting, Dedicated Server, Domain Name, and SSL Certificate :: Privacy Policy

|   
---  
|   
---  
| 

"Good services and very good customer support, thank you." **\- Keniten,IB -**  

|   
|  |    Home » Privacy Policy  
---  
| **Our Basic Privacy Policy**  
---  
  
Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.   

**What Information Do Web Collect?**  
---  
  
**1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

|   | _1.1. Credit Card Information_  
---|---  
  | If you choose to purchase products or services from us or our partners, you may need to give personal information and authorisation to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:   
• Name  
• Mailing Address  
• E-Mail Address  
• Credit Card Number  
• Home and Busines Phone Number  
• Other Personal Information (i.e. Mother's Maiden Name)   
  |    
  | _1.2. E-mail Information_  
  | In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.   
  
**2\. Web Site Use Information**  
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilises a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual   

**How Do We Use the Information You Provide to Us?**  
---  
  
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers.   

**What are Cookies?**  
---  
  
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognise the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet.   

**Notice of New Changes and Services**  
---  
  
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our client, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on a response box when you receive such an offer or by sending us an email request at [sales@imediabiz.com](mailto:sales@imediabiz.com)  

**How Do We Protect Your Information ?**  
---  
  
Information Security. We utilise encryption/security software to safeguard the Confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorised access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.  

**Evaluation of Information Protection Practices**  
---  
  
Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, Confidentiality and quality of our information.  

**Employee Access, Training and Expectations**  
---  
  
Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorised persons, processes and transactions.   

**Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties ?**  
---  
  
We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.  

**What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**  
---  
  
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.  

**Your Consent**  
---  
  
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  

**Our Policy on Data Collection**  
---  
  
In order to access certain subscriber services and restricted areas (the "Restricted Services") within the Imediabiz Web site (the "Site"), Imediabiz Pty Ltd ("Imediabiz") requires that you provide certain identifying information (the "Registration Data") listed in the online registration form. This information may include your legal name, address, telephone number(s), e-mail address, subscriber name or "screen name," areas of interest, password used to access Pay services, method of payment, and, if applicable, credit card number. Imediabiz reserves the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain your account for use of the Pay Services.  

**Confidentiality**  
---  
  
Registration Data is the property of Imediabiz, subject to and protected by the Electronic Communications Privacy Act. Imediabiz will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose your Registration Data to any third party. Imediabiz maintains a secured area on the Site for transmission of Registration Data, and stores all Registration Data in a private database which is not connected to the Internet.  

**User Access to Information Collected**  
---  
  
Registration Data is the property of Imediabiz, subject to and protected by the Electronic Communications Privacy Act. Imediabiz will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose your Registration Data to any third party. Imediabiz maintains a secured area on the Site for transmission of Registration Data, and stores all Registration Data in a private database which is not connected to the Internet.  

**Lost of Stolen Information**  
---  
  
If your credit card or password is stolen or used without your permission, immediately notify Imediabiz. Upon notification Imediabiz will cancel your credit card number and/or password and update its records. You may be unable to access certain services while Imediabiz processes the credit card and/or password change.  

**Cancellation**  
---  
  
You may cancel your account at any time by sending an e-mail to [accounting@imediabiz.com](mailto:accounting@imediabiz.com). Once Imediabiz has finished processing the cancellation, Imediabiz will delete all your Registration Data from its database.  

**Updates**  
---  
  
Imediabiz reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other company policy or practice, at any time with reasonable notice to users of the Site. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site.
